heywire.com 2014-11-28

# LiveText - Privacy

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 29, 2014.**

## 1\. DEFINITIONS & OVERVIEW

When you interact with the Services, we may collect both personal information and non-personal information from you.

**"Personal Information"** means information that specifically identifies an individual, such as name, address, telephone number or e-mail address.

**"Non-personal Information"** means information about the characteristics and activities of an individual from which any personal information has been removed, such as IP address, type of browser or mobile device used, mobile device identifier(s), aggregate interests of individuals (e.g. visits to sports sites), etc. Nothing in this policy limits our use of non-personal information.

In addition to adhering to federal and state privacy laws, we also adhere to the Mobile Marketing Association's Global Code of Conduct, guidelines established by the Internet Marketing Association and other industry guidelines in order to protect you and your identity.

The following are the basic principles that guide our actions with respect to privacy:

  1. We will **never sell or give** your personal information to any third party without your consent;
  2. We will not knowingly collect Personal Information from visitors under the age of 13;
  3. We collect certain information either directly from you, or indirectly through logs and other technologies. This information is used to provide the services to you and to provide interest-based advertising using aggregate (non-personal) information; and
  4. If you choose to access third party advertising via our Services, the advertisers may use technology to collect certain non-personal information and the use of such information is outside of our control.

**"Personal Information"** means information that specifically identifies an individual, such as name, address, telephone number or e-mail address.

**"Non-personal Information"** means information about the characteristics and activities of an individual from which any personal information has been removed, such as IP address, type of browser or mobile device used, mobile device identifier(s), aggregate interests of individuals (e.g. visits sports sites), etc. Nothing in this policy limits our use of non-personal information.

## 2\. INFORMATION THE COMPANY COLLECTS FROM YOU

**Direct Information Collection**  
When you register for Services, we collect a variety of personal information, including your name, e-mail address, date of birth, zip-postal code, country and gender. When you use the Services, we will not collect any personal information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily.

We have the right, but not the obligation, to store any messages that pass through our Services as well as other message information.

We may also receive information about you from other sources. This information may be combined with information we collect. We do not share this information with anyone except authorized third parties in aggregate (non-personal) form in connection with providing the Services.

**Automatic Information Collection**  
Using various technologies, such as cookies, pixel tags and web beacons, our systems may automatically gather information about the areas you visit through the Services and collect operational information about the technology you use, such as your browser, type of computer or mobile device, geographic location, operating systems, system and application software, peripherals, Internet service providers and the domain name of theUsing various technologies, such as cookies, pixel tags and web beacons, our systems may automatically gather information about the areas you visit through the Services and collect operational information about the technology you use, such as your browser, type of computer or mobile device, geographic location, operating systems, system and application software, peripherals, Internet service providers and the domain name of the website from which you linked to the Services. website from which you linked to the Services.

In addition, we may store some information on your computer when using HeyWire for the web. This information will be in the form of a cookie or similar file and will help us tailor the Services or advertisements to better match your interests and preferences. You can use your browser settings to control your use of cookies.

Data providers we engage, such as advertisers, may use technologies, such as cookies and pixels, to enable you to receive customized ads or content. Please note that we do not have access to or control over third parties’ cookies used in the Services, and this policy does not govern the use of cookies by these third parties. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and/or participants of the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA), which offer a single location to opt out of ad customization from their respective participating companies at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> and <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. To learn more about the entities participating in the NAI or DAA, please click on these links.

Some of our advertisers may display ads on the Services that directly solicit information, or contain technology to collect non-personal information about our users. This information is collected and used by our advertisers, and is outside of our control. If you have any questions about a banner advertisement, you should contact the responsible advertiser directly.

## 3\. HOW THE COMPANY MAY USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION

We use non-personal information collected (both directly and automatically) to:

  * help us develop, improve, deliver and operate the Services;
  * customize the Services and advertising to your preferences;
  * keep you posted on product and services announcements, important notices regarding terms, policies, and conditions;
  * detect and block security breaches and to provide you with a safe online environment;
  * support internal functions such as auditing, data analysis, research, and quality management; and 
  * to develop and deliver new products and services and to improve our Services and advertising.

We may also use the non-personal information we gather to tailor the services and advertisements to your personal interests and/or demographics (e.g., behavioral, interest-based or geographic targeted advertising). In addition, the Company may provide non-personal information in the form of aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, online traffic patterns, and related information to reputable third parties for similar purposes.

We may disclose personal information you provide via the Services to third parties only as follows:

  * to contractors we use to support our business, in which case we will require such third parties to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes;
  * in the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, dissolution, reorganization, assignment or other transfer of the Company or the business of the Services to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes;
  * to respond to law enforcement requests or where required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations; and in situations involving harassment ("cyber bullying") or threats to the physical safety of any person.

If you seek the identity of or account information about a HeyWire subscriber in connection with a civil (as opposed to criminal) legal matter, you must serve HeyWire with a valid subpoena at the address below.

Information collected and used by our advertisers is outside of our control. If you have any questions about a banner advertisement, you should contact the responsible advertiser directly. Of course, if you do not access an advertisement (tapping on an ad), no information is accessed or disclosed by such advertisement.

## 4\. INFORMATION YOU SEND

When you send a message or other content through the Services, information about you, such as your phone number, may be visible to other users. Any information you disclose to a third party through messaging is not covered by this policy.

## 5\. ACCESS TO THE INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE COMPANY

We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * You may view and modify the personal information you have provided to us by logging in to the Services and clicking on "Settings" on your device. 
  * You may also send us an e-mail message at [privacy@heywire.com](mailto:privacy@heywire.com), to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. Should you elect to have your information deleted, we will also delete your user account. However, copies of your information may remain in back up storage for some time after your deletion. We may also retain certain information to protect against identity theft or misconduct.
  * If you do not wish us to collect cookies, you may set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of the Services may not function properly.

## 6\. THIRD PARTY LINKS

From time to time, the Services may contain hyperlinks to other websites. We make no promises or guarantees regarding data collection on the hyperlinked pages that are not operated as part of the Services. We recommend that you read the privacy policy/statement for each site you visit.

## 7\. CHILDREN

We operate in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. We will not knowingly collect Personal Information from visitors under the age of 13. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and mobile applications and services and the information they disclose online. If we become aware that a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete such information. A parent or guardian may contact us directly (see contact information in Section 9 below) if they would like information deleted from our records or for further information about our policy.

## 8\. INTERNATIONAL

The Services are hosted on servers in the United States and are subject to U.S. Law.

## 9\. HOW YOU CAN CONTACT THE COMPANY

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this site, please contact us at:

MediaFriends, Inc.   
1 Canal Park, Suite 1130   
Cambridge, MA 02141 

+1 617.758.6226
